Ah, ah, what is it?
Did you come from the world of humans nya?
Are you hungry?
This cat food,
You can have some!
Even a little kindness is
Somewhere's, someone's, second hand
Formula of bad tastes
Applied to daily life
The unspoken knowledge, nya nya nya nya
Can be heard! Nya!
What are you crying about nya?
Why are you crying nya?
I don't understand, I don't understand
It's common sense in my world
The kindness of not speaking frankly
Is called "being an adult" or "hypocrisy"
That is, that is,
Common sense in the world of humans,
Right?
Heaven, and god, and fate
What about them nya
I saw people with oblong eyes
Good deeds and mischief are both, somewhere, someone's measure
And after trying hard, one would thus receive rewards
And get punishment, right?
What are you crying about nya?
Why are you crying nya?
I don't understand, I don't understand
It's common sense in my world
The blame of speaking frankly
Has become taboo, and people deceive themselves about it
That is, that is,
Common sense in the world of humans,
Right?
Affection is also unspoken understanding
Cruelty is also unspoken understanding
If the world changes, we
Will be seen as weird, right perhaps?
But here, it is like this, so
But here, it is like this, so...
What are you crying about nya?
Why are you crying nya?
I don't understand, I don't understand
It's common sense in my world
Weren't you hungry?
Then until just a while ago, we were friends,
We were, we were,
But if this is burnt deliciously, ya
Since, food
Since this is food